NGUYEN MINH ANH

0989-013-930



Frontend Developer

Ham Tan, Binh Thuan



SUMMARY

I am a Frontend Developer with over 1 year of experience, capable of problemsolving, working in teams, and working independently. My goal is to learn and develop myself to the best of my ability in both my professional field and personal life.

EDUCATION

FPT University HCM

Software Engineering 09/2019 - 12/2023

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Redux-Toolkit, Redux Saga, React-Query
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Tailwind CSS
- Ant Design, Material UI, Shadon/ui
- Git, Postman, Fork

LANGUAGES

- Vietnamese
- English

CERTIFICATIONS

- Google Project Management
- User Experience Research and Design
- Basics of Web Development & Coding

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cho Nhanh E-Commerce Company Limited

Frontend Developer | 08/2023 - Present

- **Description**: Developing an e-commerce website
- **My responsibilities:** Developing features related to user information, accounts, orders, stores, notifications, and reward points...
- **Skills:** JavaScript, Material UI, Redux-toolkit, Redux Saga...

FPT Software

Frontend Developer (Intern) | 08/2022 - 12/2022

- Description: Developing a website to manage courses, instructors, and shifts...
- **My responsibilities:** Developing features related to instructor shifts...
- **Skills:** HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Material UI, Reduxtoolkit

PROJECTS

Somo Farm Task Management

Frontend Developer | 09/2023 - 12/2023

- **Description:** Capstone project at FPT University HCM. Developing a website to manage task assignments, employees, admin, managers, and shifts for the farm
- Team size: 05
- **My responsibilities:** Developing features related to task assignments, authentication, authorization, and notifications...
- **Skills:** HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SCSS, Ant Design, Redux-Toolkit, Firebase Cloud Messaging

INTERESTS

- Football
- Badminton
- Movie

ToadTrade

Frontend Developer | 06/2022 - 08/2022

- **Description:** Developing a small website to sell used study materials and supplies for FPT University students
- Team size: 02
- My responsibilities: Developing features related to orders, products, and user information,...
- Skills: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Material UI, Redux